Hi!
Again, if you're brand new at this, just start with something small and kind of get a feel for it before you do something much larger.
If you don't want the ruler touching the photo like I did this the first and second times.
Part of the ruler is actually on the photo, but if you don't want that to be on the photo at all, then go ahead and keep it on the outside and just line it up on your photo like this.
Again, make sure that you kind of stretch out a little bit because you will be on the floor cutting for quite a bit.
If you have a nice large table to use.
You need to be able to press down, which is why I like doing it on the floor.
I have that gravity working for me and I can press down.
Again, we're going to go ahead and score this at the very top.
Again, we're just going to do it on a series of little cuts.
Pretty soon, it'll just go right through and I'll have my cardboard protecting the carpet area.
You can start to feel when it has gone all the way through your picture or through the foam core.